OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/020
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20)
1972- 2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Office of Labor-Management Standards (OLMS)
6178/020
71 cubic feet
73 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
7259140
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 30, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 21, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/008: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective bargaining--United States; Collective labor agreements- -United States; United States.; United States. Dept. of Labor--Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics--Archives
7259140
- Private agreements: Code nos.267-450 (Box 1)
  - 267, 1995-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    10/1995 - 10/2002
  - 269, 1968-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    2/1968 - 9/1996; contains Worker Agreement Booklets
  - 282, 1987-1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    8-1987 - 8-1996
  - 290, 1979-1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    5/1979 - 4/1998
  - 311, 1979-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    2/1979 - 2/1994
  - 348, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    9/1978 - 9/1984
  - 350, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    5/1987 - 5/1993
  - 374, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    8/1983
  - 397, 1980-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    5/1980 - 5/1986
  - 421, 1988-1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    6/1988 - 5/1997
  - 425 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    URW General Tire Booklets
  - 450, 1993-2002 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    10/1993 - 10/2002
- Private agreements: Code nos.8221-8537 (Box 2)
  - 8221, 2001-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 8226, 1999-2004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 8228, 1992-1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 8230, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 8327, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 8330, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 8327, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 8340, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 8341, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 8345, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 8346, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 8347, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 8395, 1999-2002 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - 8396, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - 8397, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - 8398, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - 8427, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - 8429, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - 8433, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - 8437, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - 8438, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 8447, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - 8450, 1996-2005 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - 8455, 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - 8474, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - 8475, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - 8475, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - 8476, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - 8477, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - 8479, 1998-2003 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - 8483, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - 8485, 1999-2004 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - 8486, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - 8487, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - 8488, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - 8490, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 8493, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - 8497, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 8498, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 8500, 1998-2005 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - 8501, 1999-2004 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - 8506, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - 8508, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - 8510, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - 8515, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - 8517, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - 8519, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 8522, 2000-2005 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 8524, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 8528, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 8530, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 8531, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 8532, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - 8533, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 8534, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 8535, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 8536, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 8537, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Folder List Index Box #2 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    Includes decryptions of folder contents
- Private agreements: Code nos.5727-6028 (Box 3)
  - 5727, 1974-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    8/1974 - 6/1995; contains agreement books
  - 5728, 1980-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    8/1980 - 8/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 5734, 1989-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    8/13/1989 - 8/18/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5741, 1983-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    8/7/1983 - 8/5/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 5748, 1989-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    8/1989 - 8/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 5753, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    8/1986 - 8/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 6003, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    12/1994; Contains many agreement booklets
  - 6013, 1991-1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    12/2/1991 - 12/5/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 6024, 1975-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    5/1975 - 5/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 6028, 1988-1999 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    5/1/1988 - 4/30/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index for Box #3 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1122-1223 (Box 4)
  - 1122, 1969-1985 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    3/1969 - 8/1985; contains agreement booklets
  - 1131, 1967-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    6/1967-6/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 1134, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    1/1982
  - 1135, 1982-1988 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    5/1982 - 6/1988; contains agreement booklets
  - 1202, 1984-2004 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    4/1984 - 4/30/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 1204, 1976-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    4/1976 - 6/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 1209, 1963-1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    6/1963 - 7/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 1211, 1993-2001 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    8/1993 - 8/2001; agreement booklets
  - 1222, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    5/1985 - 5/1988; contains agreement booklets
  - 1223, 1962-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    6/1962 - 6/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box #4 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Private agreements: Code nos.K3787-K4681 (Box 5)
  - 3787, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 3800, 1989-2004 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    12/1989 - 12/2004; contains agreement booklets
  - 4004, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    November 10, 2001 - February 6, 2005
  - 4005, 2000-2006 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    December 10 2000 - March 12 2006
  - 4006, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    February 26 2001 - October 28 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 4014, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    January 28 2002 - January 31 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 4015, 1998-2001 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    November 23 1998 - December 3 2001
  - 4020, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    8/31/2002 - 8/28/2004
  - 4023, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    1/1/2000 - 12/31/2003
  - 4025, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    November 15 1999 - November 17 2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 4036, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    7/19/2000 - 9/30/2003
  - 4040, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    1/1/1999 - 7/31/2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 4049, 2001-2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    August 6 2001 - July 31 2005; contains agreement booklet
  - 4050, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    June 16 2003 - June 11 2006
  - 4052, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    4/23/2001
  - 4055, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    Contains agreement booklet
  - 4056, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    9/2/2002 - 9/1/2005
  - 4057, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    9/21/2002 - 9/1/2005
  - 4058 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    Contains agreement booklet, attached to folder
  - 4065, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    28 October 2002 - 23 October 2005
  - 4066, 2000-2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    May 1 2000 - April 25 2004; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4073, 2003-2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    28 April 2003 - 9 April 2006; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4080, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    March 2 2002 - March 1 2005
  - Folder List Index Box #5 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Private agreements: Code nos.4036-4127 (Box 6)
  - 4036, 1988-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    7/1988 - 7/1997; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4051, 1992-1999 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    5/3/1992 - 5/3/1999; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4065, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    10/1992 - 10/1995; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4067, 1974-1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    11/1974 - 12/1989; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4080, 1986-2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    10/20/1986 - 3/1/2002; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4082, 1989-1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    12/1989 - 12/1998; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4092, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    10/1991; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4107, 1978-1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 4123, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    12/1991; Contains agreement booklet
  - 4127, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    7/1991; Contains agreement booklet
  - Folder List Index Box #6 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Private agreements: Code nos.8040-8219 (Box 7)
  - 8040, 2000-2005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 8042, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 8043, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 8045, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 8060, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 8062, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 8068, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 8070, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 8072, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 8079, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 8083, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 8085, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 8088, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 8093, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 8103, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 8105, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 8109, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 8111, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 8114, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 8115, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 8123, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 8124, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 8125, 2000-2005 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 8129, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 8134, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 8135, 2000-2005 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 8141, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 8153, 2003-2005 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 8155, 2003-2005 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 8157, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 8162, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 8167, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 8174, 1997-2004 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 8179, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 8181, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 8186, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 8187, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 8189, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 8193, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 8198, 2001-2005 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 8199, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 8200, 1993-1995 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 8204, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 8209, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 8213, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 8219, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Folder List Index Box #7 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Private agreements: Code nos.5207-5255 (Box 8)
  - 5207, 1985-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 5223, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - 5229, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - 5232, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Contains agreement booklet; 3/1994
  - 5234, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    3/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5235, 1991-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    3/1991 - 3/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5242, 1996-2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    5/1/1996 - 3/4/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5243, 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    6/1973 - 3/1982; contains agreement booklets
  - 5244, 1973-1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    7/1973 - 3/1982; contains agreement booklets
  - 5255, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    7/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box #8 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Private agreements: Code nos.3682-3722 (Box 9)
  - 3682, 1995-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    5/1995 - 5/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 3684, 1986-2003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    5/1986 - 5/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 3685, 1995-2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 3688, 1986-2003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    6/1986 - 5/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 3690, 1998-2003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    5/1998 - 5/2003; contains general agreement booklet
  - 3710, 1974-1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    5/1974 - 5/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 3713, 1992-2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    4/1992 - 4/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 3719, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    9/2002; contains agreement booklet
  - 3722, 1971-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    5/1971 - 5/1992; contains agreement booklets
- Private agreements: Code nos.5405-5700 (Box 10)
  - 5405, 1972-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    6/1972 - 6/1993; contains agreement newspapers
  - 5416, 1980-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    9/1980 - 9/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5417, 1962-2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    9/1962 - 9/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5421, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    9/1989 - 9/1994; contains agreement books
  - 5422, 1990-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    7/1990 - 7/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 5423, 1983-2001 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    9/1983 - 9/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5424, 1987-1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    7/1987 - 7/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 5425, 1964-2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    10/1964 - 9/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5426, 1994-2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    9/1994 - 9/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5431, 1996-2001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    10/1996 - 9/2001; contains master contract
  - 5432, 1990-2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    12/1/1990 - 9/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 5601, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    7/1997 - 6/2000; contains agreement
  - 5700, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    5/1995 - 5/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box #10 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Public agreements: Code nos.820856-830294 (Box 11)
  - 820856, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    West Coast Contra Costa Unified
  - 820858, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    City of Oklahoma City
  - 820862, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Baltimore County Administration
  - 830040, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Cherry Creek Schools
  - 830064, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Vancouver Schools District 37
  - 830095, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Board of Education Harford County
  - 830150, 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    School District of City of Detroit
  - 830166, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    District of Columbia Public Schools
  - 830174, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    Buffalo City School District
  - 830174, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Beaverton School District
  - 830177, 2000-2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Board of Education School District Philadelphia
  - 830182, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Memphis City Schools
  - 830188, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Board of School Commissioners
  - 830189, 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    New York City Board of Education
  - 830190, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 830193, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Cincinnati Board of Education
  - 830194, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 830196, 1995-1997 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Board of Education School District Detroit. MI
  - 830197, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Board of Education School District Detroit, MI
  - 830200, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    City of Long Beach
  - 830201, 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    Board of Education School District City of Detroit
  - 830202, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    Fresno Unified School District
  - 830204, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    Board of Education of Salt Lake City School District
  - 830205, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Milwaukee Board of School Directors
  - 830213, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    Phoenix Union High School District 210
  - 830207, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Newark Public School
  - 830208, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 830212, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Baltimore City Public Schools
  - 830222, 1999-2001 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Board of School Trustees Gary
  - 830224, 1997-2002 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    New York City Transit Authority
  - 830225, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    New Haven Board of Education
  - 830226, 2003-2006 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 830228, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    Board of Education Grand Rapids Public Schools
  - 830229, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - 830231, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    Milwaukee Board of School 830232
  - 830232, 1999-2003 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    City of Chicago
  - 830233, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    Oregon Health and Science University
  - 830235, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    Independent School District 347
  - 830236, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    Regent of University of Michigan
  - 830239, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    Columbus Board of Education
  - 830248, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    Board of Education
  - 830256, 2001-2004 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - 830258, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    Ohio State University (Registered Nurses)
  - 830260, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    Tucson Unified School District
  - 830261, 2004-2006 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    City of Rochester School District
  - 830262, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    New Jersey School District
  - 830263, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - 830264, 2002-2005 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    Board of County Commissioners
  - 830265, 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    Board of Education City School District NY
  - 830274, 2003-2005 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    Douglas County School District
  - Folder List Index Box #11 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Private agreements: Code nos.5701-5726 (Box 12)
  - 5701, 1992-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    5/31/1992 - 5/30/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 5703, 1989-1998 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    8/6/1989 - 8/8/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 5704, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    10/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 5707, 1977-1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    8/1977 - 8/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 5713, 1985-1997 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    6/30/1985 - 8/9/1997; contains agreement booklets
  - 5716, 1987-1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    8/1987 - 7/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 5722, 1980-1995 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 5724, 1974-1998 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    7/1974 - 6/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 5725, 1974-1998 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    8/1974 - 6/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 5726, 1980-1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    8/1980 - 6/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box #12 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Private agreements: Code nos.4022-5044 (Box 13)
  - 4022, 1996-1999 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    9/1996 - 9/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 4095, 1992-2001 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    5/1992 - 5/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 4135, 1983-1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    6/24/1983 - 9/27/1998; contains agreement booklets
  - 4207, 1997-2001 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    3/22/1997 - 3/23/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 4210, 1996-2001 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    5/1996 - 4/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 4410, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    5/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 4427, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    3/1986 - 3/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 5015, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    3/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 5022, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    3/1989
  - 5036, 1969-1975 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    2/1969 - 2/1975; contains agreement booklets
  - 5041, 1982-1990 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    11/1982 - 3/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 5044, 1979-1990 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    6/1979 - 6/1990; contains agreement
  - Folder List Index Box # 13 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Private agreements: Code nos.1940-2370 (Box 14)
  - 1940, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    10/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5787, 1973-1994 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    11/1973 - 2/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 5788, 1969-1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    11/1969 - 2/1991; contains contract booklets
  - 5785, 1972-1988 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    11/1972 - 11/1988; contains fair practice booklets
  - 5786, 1972-1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    11/1972 - 2/1994; contains contract booklets
  - 2104, 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    8/1986 - 8/1990; contains labor contracts
  - 2120, 1974-1993 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    4/1974 - 4/1993; contains agreement booklets
  - 2121, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    4/1990; contains agreement booklets
  - 2319, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - 2335, 1974-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    7/1974 - 5/1992; contains agreement booklets
  - 2337, 1985-2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    8/1985 - 8/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 2340, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    4/1999; contains agreement booklets
  - 2345, 1979-1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    5/1979 - 5/1994; contains agreement booklets
  - 2356, 1986-1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    3/1986 - 3/1993; contains contract booklets
  - 2370, 1982-1988 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    4/1982 - 4/1988; contains agreement booklets
  - Folder List Index Box # 16 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Private agreements: Code nos.6030-6865 (Box 15)
  - 6030, 1993-2000 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    1/1/1993 - 12/31/2000; contains agreement booklets
  - 6347, 1997-2003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    7/21/1997 - 6/15/2003; contains agreement booklet
  - 6350, 1994-2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    6/12/1994 - 6/15/2003; contains agreement booklets
  - 6724, 1993-2000 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    1/1993 - 1/2000; contains agreement booklets
  - 6725, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    8/1980 - 10/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 6729, 1997-2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    9/1997 - 9/2001
  - 6742, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    10/1995 - 10/1998; contains agreement booklet
  - 6753, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    4/13/1998 - 4/14/2002; contains agreement booklets
  - 6755, 1983-1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    2/1983 - 2/1992; contains contract booklets
  - 6756, 1971-1986 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    1/1/1971 - 2/28/1986
  - 6765, 1964-1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    11/1964 - 10/1996; contains agreement booklets
  - 6788, 1992-1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    10/1992 - 10/1995; contains agreement
  - 6798, 1972-1989 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    1/1972 - 9/1989; contains agreement
  - 6820, 1991-1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    9/1991 - 9/1995; contains agreement booklets
  - 6840, 1974-1989 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    8/1974 - 9/1989; contains agreement booklets
  - 6845, 1976-1997 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    6/1976 - 3/1997; contains agreement
  - 6861, 1982-2001 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    6/1982 - 6/2001; contains agreement booklets
  - 6864, 1980-1995 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    4/1980 - 9/1995; contains agreement